Guide to the Anne Dockery Photographs TAM.743
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Anne Dockery Photographs
1970-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Dockery, Anne
TAM.743
3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and one manuscript box.
Anne Dockery was a photographer with Liberation News Service. This collection consists of her black and white photographic prints of various sizes, film negatives, and color slides.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in repository; provenance is unknown.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received.
Related Materials
For more information about the Liberation News Service, see its collection, PHOTOS 022, in Tamiment Library.
Content Description
This collection consists of black and white photographic prints of various sizes, film negatives, and color slides all created by Anne Dockery, a photographer with Liberation News Service. Subjects include anti-Vietnam War marches, Gay Pride marches, Black Panthers demonstrations, the Republican National Convention, plus New York City, Northern Ireland, Hanoi, London, and Vermont.
Black-and-white photography.; Republican National Convention; Anti-war demonstrations |z United States |v Pictorial works.; Northern Ireland.; Street photography |z New York (State) |z New York
- Negatives, 1970-1995 (Box 1, Case 1-4, Box 2, Case 5-8)
- Slides - N. Ireland, New York City, Vermont, Amerherst, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Photographic prints-Liberation News Service, As You Like It, Woman Theatre, Red Balloon Day Care, Gay Pride demonstrations, NY and Washington DC demonstrations and walkouts, Detroit auto workers, United Nations General Assembly, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1-11)
- Photographic prints-women's marches, anti-war and anti-Nixon demonstrations, Comstock Prison, Dewey Canyon III, peace conferences, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1-7, 14)
- Photographic prints-Vietnam, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 8-10, 13, 31-36)
- Photographic prints-Republican National Convention, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15-19)
- Photographic prints-Civil rights demonstrations, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19, 22)
- Photographic prints-workers: loggers, meatpackers, undated (Box 3, Folder 20, 21)
- Photographic prints-Northern Ireland, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23-30)
- Miscellaneous photos, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 37-42)
- Drymounted prints, various subjects, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Later photos, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2-5)